<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KNOWtime</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="back_button_contentdescription">backbutton</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_view">Hi there, HRM: Does relying on public transit get you down?\n\n
Have you been frustrated by unreliable schedule times, waiting for your bus in bad weather, or being uncertain if you’ll arrive at your destination on time?\n\n
Well, you’re not alone. There are lots of people who share your concerns, but we’ve come up with a solution to make it better.\n\n
Introducing: KNOWtime. The Smartphone app that empowers transit riders by producing user-generated and real-time bus tracking information. With KNOWtime, people can improve their commuting experience by working together.\n\n
When riders help other riders, it’s like having a friend on every bus.\n\n
Just share your location with KNOWtime while you ride and the whole community will benefit from real-time bus tracking.\n\n
KNOWtime tracks your location, not your identity. So you can feel secure riding with us.\n\n
You can also feel good about leaving your car at home, saving gas money, reducing traffic congestion, increasing parking options downtown, and contributing to a healthier environment.\n\n
KNOWtime runs on “crowd power” – the greater the crowd, the greater the power.\n\n
So connect your friends, track your ride, and help us help you by growing our *live* local network.\n\n
When you join our community, we’ll get you where you want to go in KNOWtime.\n\n</string>
    <string name="twitter_button">twitterButton</string>
    <string name="feedback_button">feedbackButton</string>
    <string name="facebook_button">facebookButton</string>
    <string name="onmy_image">onmyimage</string>
    <string name="sendingline_image">sendinglineimage</string>
    <string name="sending_image">sendingimage</string>
    <string name="onmyway_button_image">onmywaybuttonimage</string>
    <string name="connect_to_server_image">connecttoserverimage</string>
	<string name="schedual_time">Scheduled Time</string>
	<string name="routedefault">888</string>
	<string name="gotimedefault">8888</string>
	<string name="stopstabledefault">unknown</string>
	<string name="route_name">Route Name</string>
	<string name="route_stop_fav_default">Route or Stop Name</string>
	<string name="favourite_button">Favourite Button</string>
	<string name="stops_table_header">Stops Table Header</string>
	<string name="routes_table_header">Routes Table Header</string>
	<string name="hamburger_menu_button">Hamburger Menu Button</string>
	<string name="menu_about_button">About Button</string>
	<string name="menu_shareme_button">Share Me Button</string>
	<string name="menu_stops_button">Stops Button</string>
	<string name="menu_favourite_button">Favourite Button</string>
	<string name="menu_twitter_button">Twitter Button</string>
	<string name="menu_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy Button</string>
	<string name="menu_arrow">Menu Arrow</string>
    <string name="loading_stops">Loading Stops ....</string>

</resources>
